Harrison Huston

603-630-3845 | harrison.huston@yahoo.com | linkedin.com/in/harrisonhuston/ | harrisonhuston.github.io/

SUMMARY

Software Developer with a Master of Science in Software Development from Boston University. Experience working within an Agile-Scrum SDLC methodology to produce high quality, readable, and clean code to enhance and create new features and functionality, as well as conducting software quality assurance to ensure the quality and function of code deployments and code changes.

EXPERIENCE

Revenue Solutions, Inc. (RSI) (tax software)

Senior Technical Analyst Associate (Software Developer) - Remote (2024 - Present)

- Agile-Scrum software development on tax software for governments and municipalities. Enhances and creates new features and functionality via SQL and/or Business Rules Engine (BRE) code creation and changes. Maintains and migrates code via Microsoft Visual Studio. Tracks and maintains version control and task features and functionalities through Azure DevOps. Tests and migrates deployments through the development stage and into the integration testing stage of the SDLC.

Senior Quality Assurance Associate (Software Quality Assurance and Testing) - Remote (2023 - 2024)

Quality Assurance Associate (Software Quality Assurance and Testing) - Remote (2021 - 2023)

- Agile-Scrum software quality assurance and testing on tax software for governments and municipalities. Created and maintained test cases throughout the testing process, including execution of test cases in system integration testing, creation and verification of applicable bugs, and provided necessary assistance and support for execution of test cases in user acceptance testing.

Jefferies (investment bank)

Vice President (Private Wealth Management) - Boston, MA (2019 - 2020) Series 7, 63, & 65

- Prospected and marketed private wealth management strategies and executive services to individuals, family offices, and endowments. Prospected and marketed equity and fixed income trading/research capabilities to mid-market and small sized money managers, hedge funds, and investment advisors. Facilitated access to research, analysts, and conferences to trading clients. Solicited indications of interest for capital market deals and facilitated allocations of syndicate. Conducted equity trading, booking, and settlement.

Prime Buchholz (investment consulting firm)

<u>Performance Analyst</u> - Portsmouth, NH (2019)

- Analyzed the performance and cash flows of client investments, including private equity funds, hedge funds, mutual funds, exchange traded funds, fixed income, and money markets. Prepared and disseminated monthly and quarterly client performance reports.

American Elm Distribution Partners (selling agent for Arboretum Investment Advisors)

Regional Investment Consultant - Portsmouth, NH (2018 - 2019) Series 7 & 63

- Full cycle sales of the broker-dealer fund in the western territory of the United States through the broker-dealer selling agreements. Internal wholesaling of the institutional fund to Registered Investment Advisors.

Datadog (enterprise performance monitoring software)

Account Executive - Boston, MA (2017)

- Full cycle business to business sales, focused entirely on net new logos.

ExtraHop Networks (enterprise security and performance monitoring software)

Inside Sales Representative - Remote (2016 - 2017)

- Business development and inside sales, focused entirely on scheduling meetings with net new logos.

Fidelity Investments (financial services firm)

Investment Solutions Representative - Merrimack, NH (2015 - 2016) Series 66, 7, & 63

- Assisted in retirement planning and consolidation of client accounts, including investment guidance, positioning managed accounts, positioning of Fidelity Investments for outside assets, rollovers, and transfers of assets. Facilitated trading, money movement, addressing client inquiries, and account maintenance.

Financial Representative (Full Trader) - Merrimack, NH (2014 - 2015) Series 7 & 63

- Facilitated trading, money movement, addressing client inquiries, and account maintenance.

EDUCATION

freeCodeCamp/Microsoft, Remote (2023)

- Foundational C# with Microsoft

Boston University, Boston, MA (2021 - 2023)

- Master of Science, Software Development, 3.8/4.0 GPA, Merit Scholarship Award Recipient
- Completed Coursework (Introduction to Software Development, Information Structures with Python, Data Structures and Algorithms, Advanced Programming Techniques, Data Science with Python, Artificial Intelligence, Web Application Development, Information Systems Analysis and Design, Software Design and Patterns)

University of New Hampshire, Durham, NH (2010 - 2014)

- Bachelor of Science, University of New Hampshire Sales Club (2014), Wildcat Sports Properties, Advertising & Sales Intern (2013 - 2014), Over 75 Hours of Unpaid Volunteerism (2014)